Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Classified Photographs
  - Toledo & Western
    - Freight motor and boxcar 204, [TW35] (Box 2)
    - Boxcars 206, 203, and 207, [TW36] (Box 2)
    - Cattle car 301, [TW37] (Box 2)
    - Ballast car 504, [TW38] (Box 2)
    - Engine 400 and ballast train, [TW39] (Box 2)
    - Freight motor 103 and ballast train, [TW40] (Box 2)
    - Work train in yard, [TW41] (Box 2)
  - University of Michigan
    (Code UM)
    - Electric locomotive, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1941, [UM1-2] (Box 2)
    - Electric locomotive, [UM3-6] (Box 2)
  - Terre Haute & Logansport (Vandalia Line)
    (Code Van)
    - Engine 101, [Van1] (Box 2)
  - Wabash
    (Code W)
    - Engine 670, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1947, [W1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 692, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1947, [W2] (Box 2)
    - Engine 2201 Ann Arbor, Mich. 1947, [W3] (Box 2)
    - Engine 185, [W4] (Box 2)
    - Diesel engine 1020 on football train, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1951, [W5-6] (Box 2)
    - Engine 617, [W7] (Box 2)
    - Engine 673 on football train, Ann Arbor, Mich., [W8-8a] (Box 2)
      (no print for W8a)
    - Engine 2264, [W9] (Box 2)
    - Engine 414, [W10] (Box 2)
    - Engine 2815 and freight train, Whitaker, Mich., [W11] (Box 2)
  - Wheeling & Lake Erie
    (Code WLE)
    - Engine 70, Huron, Ohio circa 1895, [WLE1] (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous
    (Code X)
    - Freight cars on siding, northern Michigan circa 1890, [X1] (Box 2)
    - Pacific-type locomotive, Wenona Beach, Bay City, Mich. 1948, [X2-3] (Box 2)
      (no print for X2)
    - Model locomotive, Pacific type, [X4-5] (Box 2)
    - Levers in interlocking plant, Annpere, Mich. 1937, [X6] (Box 2)
    - Balloon horse car, San Francisco, Calif. 1870, [X7] (Box 2)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers monument, Marshall, Mich., [X9-10] (Box 2)
    - Amusement park engine Shirley, Lake Lansing, Mich. 1938, [X12] (Box 2)
    - Amusement park engine, Montpelier, Ohio 1958, [X13] (Box 2)
    - Four engines on snowplow, [X14] (Box 2)
    - "Your humble servant at the age of six", [X15] (Box 2)
      Stoner and drawing of locomotive
- Unclassified Photographs
  unless otherwise noted the collection contains only a print of each item
  The Unclassified photos series (Box 2) contains photos Stoner did not, for some reason, classify and add to his main series. Coverage in this series is similar to the Classified photos series, but includes more non-Michigan photos. Negatives for a few of these photos are found in the Unclassified negatives series. The photos in this series are arranged alphabetically by the name of the railroad represented. The collection does not include any log created by Stoner for this series, and the negative sleeves do not include any information beyond what is included in this finding aid. These photos generally are not as well identified as those in the Classified photos series. Photos in this series are indexed by railroad name and topic.
  - Ann Arbor Railroad
    - Engines 7-202
      - Engine 7 (Box 2)
      - Engine 10 (Box 2)
      - Engine 18? (Box 2)
      - Engine 31 (Box 2)
      - Engine 34, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 51 (Box 2)
      - Engine 120, 6 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 121, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 126 (Box 2)
      - Engine 141, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 151, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 152 (Box 2)
      - Engine 153, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 158 (Box 2)
      - Engine 161 (Box 2)
      - Engine 172 (Box 2)
      - Engine 202 (Box 2)
    - Engines 1611-2553 and diesels
      - Engine 1611, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 1612, 4 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 1614, 6 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2171 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2172, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2173 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2175 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2175 and Wabash Engine 2201 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2178 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2480, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2481, 5 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2482, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2490, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2491 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2492, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 2494 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2553 (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 1, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 2 (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 3 (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 7, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 50, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Diesel engine 52, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Wrecks
      - Ann Arbor, Mich. (Box 2)
        (negative available)
      - Ann Arbor, Mich., 6 photographs (Box 2)
      - Ann Arbor, Mich., on bridge over Huron River, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Ann Arbor, Mich. 1951, 8 photographs (Box 2)
      - Between Hamburg and Lakeland, Mich. 1908 (Box 2)
      - Foundered carferry interior, Manistique, Mich. (Box 2)
      - Marion, Mich., wreck of Engine 204 1912, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      - Millersville, Mich., snow blockade 1924, 8 photographs (Box 2)
      - Sherman, Mich., wreck of Engine 44 1899 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Caboose (Box 2)
      - Carferries, Frankfort, Mich., 5 photographs (Box 2)
        (negative available for one)
      - Carferry entering Frankfort, Mich., harbor, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Coach car (Box 2)
      - Freight car (Box 2)
      - Freight train, Unidentified, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Motorcar, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Railroad station, Unidentified (Box 2)
      - Timetable (Box 2)
      - Track repairers (Box 2)
  - Ann Arbor Street Railway
    - Car 2 (Box 2)
  - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe
    - Diesel engine, 4 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 3741 (Box 2)
    - Freight cars, 6 photographs (Box 2)
  - Au Sable & Northwestern
    - Ruined engine 1911 (Box 2)
  - Baltimore & Ohio
    - Diesel engine 60 (Box 2)
    - Engine Atlantic and coaches, 5 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Thos. Jefferson (Box 2)
    - Engine Tom Thumb, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Wm. Galloway (Box 2)
    - Engine Wm. Mason, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 57, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 73 (Box 2)
    - Engine 117, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 198 (Box 2)
    - Engine 200 (Box 2)
    - Engine 217 (Box 2)
    - Engine 600 (Box 2)
    - Engine 875, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 2862 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5320 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Blaney & Southern
    - Auto before conversion to rail service (Box 2)
    - Engine (Box 2)
    - Engine 45 (Box 2)
  - Boyne City & Southeastern
    - Engine 2 (Box 2)
  - Cadillac, Mich., views
    - Cummer-Diggins camp (Box 2)
      (negative available na6491)
    - Lumber yard 1896 (Box 2)
      (negative available na6492)
  - Calumet & Hecla
    - Engine Osceola (Box 2)
  - Canadian National
    - Engine 6403 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Canadian Pacific
    - Engine 2856 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2926 (Box 2)
  - Central Pacific
    - Engine 1 (Box 2)
    - Engine 3 (Box 2)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio
    - Engine 1602 and train (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Chicago & North Western
    - Engine 3010, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 3011 (Box 2)
    - Engine 3024 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 5 photographs (Box 2)
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy
    - Burlington Zephyr (Box 2)
    - Engine 9 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 4 photographs (Box 2)
  - Cincinnati, Jackson & Mackinaw
    - Engine 30 (Box 2)
  - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis
    - Engine 381 (Box 2)
    - Engine 6456 (Box 2)
  - Columbus, Chicago & Indiana Central
    - Engine 369 (Box 2)
  - Cummer Sons Cypress Co.
    - Log loader 1961 (Box 2)
    - Mill, Lacoochee, Fla. 1961 (Box 2)
  - Detroit & Lima Northern
    - Engine 7 (Box 2)
    - Engine 67 (Box 2)
    - Car 100 (Box 2)
  - Detroit & Mackinac
    - Construction and fight with Michigan Central, Cheboygan, Mich. 1904, 13 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine (Box 2)
    - Engine 22 (Box 2)
    - Engine 24 (Box 2)
    - Engine 135 (Box 2)
    - Engine 139, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Detroit & Milwaukee
    - Engine 30 (Box 2)
    - Engine Ovid (Box 2)
    - Engine Pontiac (Box 2)
  - Detroit & River St. Clair Railway
    - Car 5 (Box 2)
  - Detroit & Toledo Shore Line
    - Engine 6 (Box 2)
    - Engine 7 (Box 2)
    - Engine 15 (Box 2)
    - Engine 25 (Box 2)
    - Engine 102 (Box 2)
    - Engine 103 (Box 2)
  - Detroit, Grand Rapids & Western
    - Engine 6 and train (Box 2)
  - Detroit, Lansing & Northern
    - Engine 8 and first train into Lake Odessa, Mich. 1888 (Box 2)
  - Detroit River Tunnel Co.
    (these photos formerly part of an album)
    - First official trip through tunnel 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 1)
    - W.C. Brown special 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 2)
    - Sketch of tunnel (Box 2)
      (no. 3)
    - Map of tunnel vicinity (Box 2)
      (no. 4)
    - Windsor, Ont., yards 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 5-6)
    - Making first run through tunnel 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 7-8)
    - Tunnel excavation 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 9)
    - Tunnel excavation 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 10)
    - Tunnel excavation 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 11-12)
    - Ventilator construction 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 13)
    - Open cut construction 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 14-17)
    - Tunnel construction 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 18)
    - Detroit portal 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 19-20)
    - Coffer dam construction 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 21-23)
    - Coffer dam 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 24)
    - Coffer dam 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 26-27)
    - Coffer dam and approach tunnel 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 28-29)
    - Air lock 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 30)
    - Joint tests 1907-1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 31)
    - Dredges, sounding raft, divers scow 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 32)
    - Dredges 1907-1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 33-34)
    - Tunnel section construction 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 35-36)
    - Launching tunnel sections 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 37)
    - Sinking tunnel section 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 38-42)
    - Sinking tunnel section 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 43-46)
    - Sinking tunnel section 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 47-48)
    - Tunnel section ready to launch 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 49)
    - Sinking tunnel section 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 50-52)
    - Tunnel section ready to launch 1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 53)
    - Sinking tunnel section 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 54-70)
    - Tremie scow 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 71)
    - Tunnel excavation 1907-1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 72-75)
    - Tunnel before lining 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 76-78)
    - Tunnel lined 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 79-80)
    - Tunnel bulkhead 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 81-82)
    - Open cut construction 1907-1908 (Box 2)
      (no. 83-85)
    - Cut and cover construction 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 86-87)
    - Approach tunnel (Box 2)
      (no. 88-89)
    - Approach tracks, Detroit, Mich. (Box 2)
      (no. 90)
    - Test train and yard, Detroit, Mich. (Box 2)
      (no. 91)
    - Yards, Detroit, Mich. (Box 2)
      (no. 92)
    - Yards, Detroit, Mich. 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 93)
    - Approach tracks, Windsor, Ont. (Box 2)
      (no 94)
    - Approach tracks, Windsor, Ont. 1910 (Box 2)
      (no 95)
    - Locomotive shed, Windsor, Ont. (Box 2)
      (no. 96-97)
    - Switch, Windsor, Ont. (Box 2)
      (no. 98-99)
    - Windsor, Ont., open cut (Box 2)
      (no. 100)
    - Test train approaching Windsor, Ont., portal 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 101)
    - Windsor, Ont., yards (Box 2)
      (no. 102)
    - Electric locomotive leaving tunnel, Detroit, Mich. (Box 2)
      (no. 103)
    - Tunnel 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 104-105)
    - Substation foundation 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 106)
    - Substation and yards 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 107)
    - Substation 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 108)
    - Motor generator room (Box 2)
      (no. 109-110)
    - Battery room 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 111)
    - Field offices, Detroit, Mich., and Windsor, Ont. 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 112)
    - Cement testing facility, Detroit, Mich. 1907 (Box 2)
      (no. 113)
    - First work on cut for new depot 1909 (Box 2)
      (no. 114)
    - Electric locomotive in approach tunnel (Box 2)
      (no. 115)
    - Test train in open cut, Detroit, Mich. 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 116)
    - Open cut and portal, Windsor, Ont. 1910 (Box 2)
      (no. 117-118)
    - Yards (Box 2)
      (no. 119)
  - Detroit Terminal Railroad
    - Engine 12 (Box 2)
    - Engine 32 (Box 2)
    - Engine 203 (Box 2)
  - Detroit, Toledo & Ironton
    - Engine 73 (Box 2)
    - Engine 251 (Box 2)
    - Engine 803 (Box 2)
  - Duluth, Missabe & Iron Range
    - Engine 227 (Box 2)
  - Duluth, South Shore & Atlantic
    - Engine 42 (Box 2)
    - Engine 90 (Box 2)
    - Engine 500 (Box 2)
    - Engine 550 (Box 2)
  - Empire & South Eastern
    - Engine 4 (Box 2)
  - Escanaba & Lake Superior
    - Engine 8 (Box 2)
    - Engine 14 (Box 2)
  - Famous engines and trains
    - Engine, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Camden (Box 2)
    - Engine DeWitt Clinton and coaches, 9 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine General, Western & Atlantic, 5 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Genl. Haupt, U.S. Military Railroad (Box 2)
    - Engine Hackensack, Hackensack & New York (Box 2)
    - Engine Jay Gould (Box 2)
    - Engine Pioneer, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Rocket (Box 2)
    - Engine Sabine, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine Sam Hale, Atlantic & Gulf (Box 2)
    - Gov. Murphy's special train 1937, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Railroad exhibit, Chicago, Ill. 1934 (Box 2)
    - Royal Scot train, 5 photographs (Box 2)
  - Flint & Pere Marquette
    - Engine 44 (Box 2)
    - Railroad yard, Unidentified (Box 2)
  - Frankfort, Mich., views
    - Construction(?) (Box 2)
    - Harbor and town, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Hunting camp (Box 2)
    - Life saving crew (Box 2)
    - Life saving drill, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Life saving station (Box 2)
    - Log drive (Box 2)
    - Motorboat Gotland (Box 2)
    - Ruins of Hotel Frontenac (Box 2)
    - Sailboat (Box 2)
    - Schooner, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Ship's crew (Box 2)
    - Steamer entering Frankfort harbor (Box 2)
    - Steamer in front of Hotel Frontenac, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      (negative available for two)
    - Steamer in harbor (Box 2)
    - Tent meeting (Box 2)
    - Town and mills (Box 2)
    - Town and rural area (Box 2)
  - General Motors
    - Train of Tomorrow, 8 photographs (Box 2)
  - Grand Ledge, Mich., views
    - View of town (Box 2)
  - Grand Rapids & Indiana
    - Engine 10 (Box 2)
    - Engine 68 (Box 2)
    - Engine 105 (Box 2)
    - Engines 51, 53, and 54 and snow plow, Suttons Bay, Mich. circa 1906 (Box 2)
      (negative available na7910)
  - Grand Trunk Western
    - Engines 117-1502
      - Engine 117 (Box 2)
      - Engine 299 (Box 2)
      - Engine 303 (Box 2)
      - Engine 544 (Box 2)
      - Engine 629 (Box 2)
      - Engine 901 (Box 2)
      - Engine 951 (Box 2)
      - Engine 992 (Box 2)
      - Engine 1100 (Box 2)
      - Engine 1222 (Box 2)
      - Engine 1502 (Box 2)
    - Engines 2671-8340 and miscellaneous
      - Engine 2671 (Box 2)
      - Engine 2672 (Box 2)
      - Engine 3524 (Box 2)
      - Engine 3754 (Box 2)
      - Engine 4070 (Box 2)
      - Engine 5628 (Box 2)
      - Engine 5630 (Box 2)
      - Engine 5632, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 6038 (Box 2)
      - Engine 6040 (Box 2)
      - Engine 6319 (Box 2)
      - Engine 6406, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 6409 (Box 2)
      - Engine 8340 (Box 2)
      - Railfan train 1960, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Hecla & Torch Lake
    - Engine Cartier (Box 2)
    - Engine Champlain (Box 2)
    - Engine Penokee (Box 2)
  - Illinois Central
    - Engine Mississippi (Box 2)
    - Engine 1 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1401 (Box 2)
    - Loading train with barrels of fruit (Box 2)
  - Industrial railroads
    - H.C. Johnson Co. (Box 2)
    - Engine 2 (Box 2)
    - Huron Milling Co.(?), Harbor Beach, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Switch engine (Box 2)
    - Michigan Alkali Co. (Box 2)
    - Engine 8 (Box 2)
  - Jennings, Mich., views
    - Lumber mills, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      (negative available na6487-na6489)
    - Mitchell Bros. department store (Box 2)
      (negative available na6490)
    - Street scene (Box 2)
      (negative available na6486)
  - Keweenaw Central
    - Engine 20 (Box 2)
  - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern
    - Engine 48, Lansing, Mich. circa 1896 (Box 2)
    - Engine 485 (Box 2)
  - Lake Superior & Ishpeming
    - Engine 19 (Box 2)
    - Engine 23 (Box 2)
  - Logging and logging railroads
    - Big wheels (Box 2)
    - Engine in park, Traverse City, Mich., 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - High Bluff Narrow Gauge Railroad (Box 2)
    - Raine & Raine engine, Rainestown, Pa. (Box 2)
    - Stratford, Mich., plaque (Box 2)
  - Manistique & Lake Superior
    - Engine 2370 Manistique, Mich. 1951 (Box 2)
  - Michigan Central
    - Engine 124 (Box 2)
      (negative available na4747)
    - Engine 499 (Box 2)
    - Sterling's Photograph Gallery car (Box 2)
    - Train leaving Ann Arbor, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Wreck, Chelsea, Mich. (Box 2)
  - Mount Washington Cog Railway
    - Train on Jacob's Ladder (Box 2)
  - Muskegon Railway & Navigation Co.
    - Engine 1 (Box 2)
  - Nahma & Northern
    - Engine 4 (Box 2)
  - New York Central
    - Diesel engines 4000 and 4001 (Box 2)
    - Engine 170 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2000(?) (Box 2)
    - Engine 3350 (Box 2)
    - Engine 3406 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5341 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5352 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5444, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 5445, 4 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 5454, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 6340 and Gov. Dewey's special train 1944 (Box 2)
    - Engine 7820 (Box 2)
    - Engine 8210 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Mercury (Box 2)
    - Train leaving Ann Arbor, Mich. 1939 (Box 2)
  - New York Central & Hudson River
    - Engine 999, 6 photographs (Box 2)
  - Norfolk & Western
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Peerless Portland Cement Co.
    - Loading cars on barge, 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad
    - Engine John Bull (Box 2)
    - Engine 472 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1052 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2490 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2760 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5354, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 5363 (Box 2)
    - Engine 5400 (Box 2)
    - Engine 6598 (Box 2)
    - Engine 6813 (Box 2)
    - Engine 7067 (Box 2)
    - Engine 7335 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Pere Marquette
    - Caboose (Box 2)
    - Diesel engine (Box 2)
    - Diesel engine 101, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Diesel engine 102 (Box 2)
    - Diesel engine 103 (Box 2)
    - Engine 295 (Box 2)
    - Engine 298 (Box 2)
    - Engine 375 (Box 2)
    - Engine 504 (Box 2)
    - Engine 721 (Box 2)
    - Engine 917 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1004 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1008 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1012, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 1019 (Box 2)
    - Engine 1202, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 1338 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Road machine (Box 2)
    - Wrecker (Box 2)
  - Railroad stations
    - Adrian, Mich. (Box 2)
      (negative available na9950)
    - Ann Arbor, Mich., MC station (Box 2)
    - Annpere, Mich., 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Bay View, Mich., GR&I station (Box 2)
    - Chelsea, Mich., MC station (Box 2)
    - Dexter, Mich., MC station (Box 2)
    - Kalamazoo, Mich., CK&S station (Box 2)
    - Marshall, Mich., NYC station (Box 2)
      (negative available na9951)
    - Milford, Mich. (Box 2)
      (negative available na9949)
    - Mount Dora, Fla. (Box 2)
    - Peterboro, N.H.(?) (Box 2)
    - Petoskey, Mich., PM station (Box 2)
    - Pompeii, Mich., GT station (Box 2)
    - Roscommon, Mich., NYC station (Box 2)
    - Spring Arbor, Mich., 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Trenary, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Warsaw, Ind., Big Four station (Box 2)
    - Unidentified Ann Arbor station (Box 2)
  - St. Clair Tunnel Co.
    - Engine 598 (Box 2)
  - Shay
    - Hemlock Central log train (Box 2)
    - Shay business card with cut of engine (Box 2)
    - Shay engine (Box 2)
    - Shay engine, Drawing (Box 2)
    - Shay house, Harbor Springs, Mich., 3 photographs (Box 2)
  - Ships
    - Freighter J.P. Morgan Jr. (Box 2)
    - Freighter John Sherman (Box 2)
  - Soo Line
    - Engine 600 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Southern
    - Engine 1334 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
    - Three level bridge, Richmond, Va. (Box 2)
  - Southern Pacific
    - Engine 22 (Box 2)
    - Engine 4410 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
  - Sykes, W.L.
    - Log train, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Union Pacific
    - Engine 58, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1939 (Box 2)
    - Engine 4002 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 4 photographs (Box 2)
    - Snow machine competition 1890, 14 photographs (Box 2)
      (negatives available for 3 photos)
    - Streamline train, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - University of Michigan views
    - Carillon (Box 2)
    - Fountain, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Haven Hall (Box 2)
  - Wabash
    - Engine 253 (Box 2)
    - Engine 513 (Box 2)
    - Engine 546 (Box 2)
    - Engine 565 (Box 2)
    - Engine 601 (Box 2)
    - Engine 608 (Box 2)
    - Engine 644 (Box 2)
    - Engine 659 (Box 2)
    - Engine 670 (Box 2)
    - Engine 705 (Box 2)
    - Engine 774 (Box 2)
    - Engine 835 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2030 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2201, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 2209 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2218, 2 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 2257, 3 photographs (Box 2)
    - Engine 2259 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2442 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2720 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2806 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2910 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2921 (Box 2)
    - Freight car (Box 2)
    - Passenger cars (Box 2)
    - Test car, 4 photographs (Box 2)
    - Track machine (Box 2)
  - Wheeling & Lake Erie
    - Engine 87 (Box 2)
    - Freight car, 2 photographs (Box 2)
  - Wisconsin Land & Lumber Co.
    - Engine 1 (Box 2)
    - Engine 2 (Box 2)
  - Wyandotte Southern
    - Engine 5 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Freight cars, 28 photographs (Box 2)
    - Locomotives (line identified)
      - Bradford & Foster Brook
        - Engine, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Chicago Great Western
        - Engine 866 (Box 2)
      - Columbia & Nehalem River
        - Engine 122 (Box 2)
      - Denver & Rio Grande
        - Engine 168, 4 photographs (Box 2)
      - Detroit Zoo
        - Miniature train (Box 2)
      - Ghost Town & Calico
        - Engine 41 and train (Box 2)
      - Lehigh Valley
        - Engine 1 (Box 2)
      - Louisville & Nashville
        - Engine 1898 and train (Box 2)
      - Louisville, New Albany & Corydon
        - Engine 5 (Box 2)
      - Manitou & Pike's Peak
        - Engine 2, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Natchez & Hamburg
        - Engine Mississippi (Box 2)
      - New York, Chicago & St. Louis
        - Engine 170 (Box 2)
      - Pere Marquette Jr.
        - Miniature train (Box 2)
      - Rio Grande Southern
        - Engine 20 and train (Box 2)
        - Engine 346 and train (Box 2)
      - St. Louis-San Francisco
        - Engine 641 (Box 2)
      - St. Paul & Pacific
        - Engine Wm. Crooks (Box 2)
      - Temiskaming & Northern Ontario
        - Engine 137 (Box 2)
        - Engine 1102 (Box 2)
      - Tonopah & Tidewater
        - Engine 8 (Box 2)
      - U.S. Government
        - Engine 5255 (Box 2)
      - West Feliciana
        - Engine 200 (Box 2)
    - Locomotives (line unidentified)
      - Detail of engine (Box 2)
      - Engine, 3 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine (TB&CR RR?) (Box 2)
      - Engine and crew, 4 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine and train, 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine and train at railroad museum (?) (Box 2)
      - Engine at gravel pit (?), 2 photographs (Box 2)
      - Engine 5 (H&C RR) (Box 2)
      - Engine 8 (H&C RR) (Box 2)
      - Engine 9 (Box 2)
      - Engine 123(?) and train (Box 2)
      - Engine 129 (John Stupplefield) (Box 2)
      - Engine 210 (CH&D) (Box 2)
      - Engine 425 and train (Box 2)
      - Engine 23883 (August Lindstrom) (Box 2)